{
  "apikey": "%PUT-YOUR-API-KEY-HERE%",
  "description": "This is simple calibration data used for testing purposes. Do not use it in production environment!",
  "copyright": "Copyright (C) 2238 by BanAN Technologies Inc.",
  "test-data": [
    {
      "question": "87 + 77",
      "answer": 164
    },
    {
      "question": "62 + 56",
      "answer": 118
    },
    {
      "question": "23 + 17",
      "answer": 40
    },
    {
      "question": "86 + 65",
      "answer": 151
    },
    {
      "question": "50 + 41",
      "answer": 91
    },
    {
      "question": "40 + 94",
      "answer": 134
    },
    {
      "question": "22 + 49",
      "answer": 71
    },
    {
      "question": "25 + 42",
      "answer": 67
    },
    {
      "question": "52 + 75",
      "answer": 127
    },
    {
      "question": "70 + 58",
      "answer": 128
    },
    {
      "question": "53 + 74",
      "answer": 127
    },
    {
      "question": "61 + 52",
      "answer": 113
    },
    {
      "question": "85 + 60",
      "answer": 145
    },
    {
      "question": "72 + 5",
      "answer": 77
    },
    {
      "question": "56 + 94",
      "answer": 150
    },
    {
      "question": "12 + 34",
      "answer": 46
    },
    {
      "question": "85 + 30",
      "answer": 115
    },
    {
      "question": "78 + 15",
      "answer": 93
    },
    {
      "question": "70 + 71",
      "answer": 141
    },
    {
      "question": "31 + 95",
      "answer": 126
    },
    {
      "question": "70 + 14",
      "answer": 84
    },
    {
      "question": "33 + 37",
      "answer": 70
    },
    {
      "question": "83 + 4",
      "answer": 87
    },
    {
      "question": "93 + 35",
      "answer": 128
    },
    {
      "question": "96 + 92",
      "answer": 188
    },
    {
      "question": "8 + 8",
      "answer": 16
    },
    {
      "question": "13 + 23",
      "answer": 36
    },
    {
      "question": "40 + 88",
      "answer": 128
    },
    {
      "question": "68 + 93",
      "answer": 161
    },
    {
      "question": "60 + 56",
      "answer": 116
    },
    {
      "question": "60 + 18",
      "answer": 78
    },
    {
      "question": "2 + 97",
      "answer": 99
    },
    {
      "question": "19 + 1",
      "answer": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "22 + 65",
      "answer": 87
    },
    {
      "question": "60 + 21",
      "answer": 81
    },
    {
      "question": "100 + 40",
      "answer": 140
    },
    {
      "question": "39 + 24",
      "answer": 63
    },
    {
      "question": "47 + 3",
      "answer": 50
    },
    {
      "question": "95 + 14",
      "answer": 109
    },
    {
      "question": "19 + 100",
      "answer": 119
    },
    {
      "question": "43 + 55",
      "answer": 98
    },
    {
      "question": "68 + 52",
      "answer": 120
    },
    {
      "question": "48 + 29",
      "answer": 77
    },
    {
      "question": "52 + 38",
      "answer": 90
    },
    {
      "question": "62 + 10",
      "answer": 72
    },
    {
      "question": "47 + 94",
      "answer": 141
    },
    {
      "question": "28 + 83",
      "answer": 111
    },
    {
      "question": "24 + 29",
      "answer": 53
    },
    {
      "question": "10 + 64",
      "answer": 74
    },
    {
      "question": "54 + 31",
      "answer": 85
    },
    {
      "question": "89 + 89",
      "answer": 178
    },
    {
      "question": "77 + 27",
      "answer": 104
    },
    {
      "question": "50 + 49",
      "answer": 99
    },
    {
      "question": "46 + 54",
      "answer": 100
    },
    {
      "question": "17 + 28",
      "answer": 45
    },
    {
      "question": "68 + 4",
      "answer": 72
    },
    {
      "question": "62 + 6",
      "answer": 68
    },
    {
      "question": "52 + 40",
      "answer": 92
    },
    {
      "question": "70 + 94",
      "answer": 164
    },
    {
      "question": "31 + 28",
      "answer": 59
    },
    {
      "question": "22 + 55",
      "answer": 77
    },
    {
      "question": "16 + 59",
      "answer": 75
    },
    {
      "question": "73 + 99",
      "answer": 172
    },
    {
      "question": "36 + 29",
      "answer": 65
    },
    {
      "question": "16 + 81",
      "answer": 97
    },
    {
      "question": "59 + 63",
      "answer": 122
    },
    {
      "question": "49 + 11",
      "answer": 60
    },
    {
      "question": "14 + 99",
      "answer": 113
    },
    {
      "question": "8 + 17",
      "answer": 25
    },
    {
      "question": "19 + 39",
      "answer": 58
    },
    {
      "question": "74 + 13",
      "answer": 87
    },
    {
      "question": "99 + 31",
      "answer": 130
    },
    {
      "question": "89 + 78",
      "answer": 167
    },
    {
      "question": "21 + 77",
      "answer": 98
    },
    {
      "question": "70 + 8",
      "answer": 78
    },
    {
      "question": "26 + 2",
      "answer": 28
    },
    {
      "question": "27 + 92",
      "answer": 119
    },
    {
      "question": "71 + 81",
      "answer": 152
    },
    {
      "question": "77 + 81",
      "answer": 158
    },
    {
      "question": "12 + 22",
      "answer": 34
    },
    {
      "question": "41 + 17",
      "answer": 58
    },
    {
      "question": "18 + 41",
      "answer": 59
    },
    {
      "question": "82 + 46",
      "answer": 128
    },
    {
      "question": "7 + 99",
      "answer": 106
    },
    {
      "question": "80 + 52",
      "answer": 132
    },
    {
      "question": "63 + 51",
      "answer": 114
    },
    {
      "question": "97 + 32",
      "answer": 129
    },
    {
      "question": "19 + 78",
      "answer": 97
    },
    {
      "question": "33 + 4",
      "answer": 37
    },
    {
      "question": "1 + 1",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "89 + 42",
      "answer": 131
    },
    {
      "question": "42 + 57",
      "answer": 99
    },
    {
      "question": "74 + 47",
      "answer": 121
    },
    {
      "question": "76 + 57",
      "answer": 133
    },
    {
      "question": "71 + 82",
      "answer": 153
    },
    {
      "question": "19 + 65",
      "answer": 84
    },
    {
      "question": "34 + 88",
      "answer": 122
    },
    {
      "question": "13 + 84",
      "answer": 97
    },
    {
      "question": "78 + 95",
      "answer": 173
    },
    {
      "question": "73 + 33",
      "answer": 106
    }
  ],
  "chunk": {
    "number": 10,
    "total": 22,
    "size": 100,
    "range": {
      "from": 900,
      "to": 1000
    }
  }
}